Samiya

Nasir

CONTACT

Voice: + 92 332 4265964

snasir819@gmail.com

Lahore, Pakistan

PROFILE

Hard-working ,professional with 2+ years of experience and a proven knowledge in the field of education, administration, accounts, customer support, data entry at any professional institution or firm providing equal opportunity of learning and growth.

Ability to work in a challenging environment.

KNOWLEDGE OF/ CERTIFICATIONS

- MS Office
- SAP, XERO
- Data Entry
- Accountancy and management
- Planning and Organization
- Developing Professionalism
- Commercial Awareness.

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Solid communicator.
- Good presentation skills.
- 50+ words per minute typing speed.
- English, Urdu, Punjabi and a little bit of Arabic.

Have a clear and professional sounding voice.

EDUCATION:-

ACCA:

F-level exempted

Professional Level in process

Masters in Accountancy and Finance:

University of Lahore (CGPA - 3.99)

B.Com (Bachelors of Commerce):

The University of Punjab, Lahore 2018-19 (1st division)

Intermediate in Commerce group:

Pakistan International School Jeddah (FBISE) 2016 – 17 (1st division)

Matriculation in Humanities group:

Pakistan International School Jeddah (FBISE) 2014 – 15 (1st division)

WORK EXPERIENCE:-

<u>July 2021-Nov 2021:-</u> Accounts and finance Intern at Hivemetrics (SMC PVT.) ltd.

<u>Jan 2019 – April 2019</u> worked as a cashier in a renowned salon of Jeddah K.S.A

<u>Aug 2018 – Jan 2019</u> worked as an account manager at a private school based in Jeddah K.S.A

<u>Sep 2016- Jan 2018</u> worked as a kindergarten and higher grades teacher at AL TAWFIQ INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL JEDDAH, K.S.A

<u>Academic Experience:-</u> Classes were given for 3 years from kindergarten to Grade 8 students. Accounting and commerce related subjects classes were also given . (I.COM AND B.COM)

PARTICIPATIONS / ACHIEVEMENTS:-

- Having command and got awards for best presentations and projects related to my field.
- Managed to be in sports and academic field both as a position holder,
- Organised several occasions and events during my work.
- Several certificates related to accounts, finance, Ms office, marketing etc., are obtained online .(Becker, Great learning, Skillzcafe, Umedy, CFI & Google Digital Garage)

SCHOLARSHIPS:-

30% performance based scholarship in the annual tuition fees at University of Lahore.

REFERENCES

Available on request.